Preliminary Guide to the John A. Wilson papers, 1974-1993 MS2190
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Subject files, 1974-1993; Series 3
  This series contains legislation, reports, correspondence, publications, clippings, photographs, posters, artifacts, and memorial materials documenting the political career of John A. Wilson. Subject files include information on issues, legislation, and organizations and buildings within the city. The material dates from 1974-1993.
  - 1200 Delaware Ave SW, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - 1201 K Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 1227 - 10th Street NW - 10th and O Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 1305 Riggs St. NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - 1423 R Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - 1423 R Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - 14th and Q St. NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - 14th Grantee Performance Report, 1988 November 30; Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - 1619 R Street NW, 1983; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - 1727 R Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - 17th Street Merchants, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - 203 N Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - 4th and M Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 500 Block L Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 600 Eye Street SW Vibration, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - 601 L Street NE, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 7-264 Linkage - Notes - Memos, 1987; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 8 Day Pre-Primary Report, 1984 September 03; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 22)
  - 8-306 - Outside income limitation, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 8-day pre-general report, 1988 November 01; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 8-day pre-primary reports, 1988 September 06; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - 900 Block - L Street Coalition, undated; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - A.L. Nellum, 1980; Series 3 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - ABC Law, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - ABC Law Changes, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - ABC Law Changes, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - ABC Legislation, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - ABC Legislation, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - ABC Legislation - limiting licenses, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - ABC Legislation - testimony, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - ABC Reform Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 16)
  - ABC Reform Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - ABC Reform Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - ABC Reform Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - ABC Regulations, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - ABC Regulations, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - ABC Rules Hearing Testimony, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - ABC version two - workpapers, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Abenet Tessema - Letter of opposition ABC Board, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Abortion, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Abortions, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Academic robes, Series 3 (Box 83, Item 7)
  - ADL Report, 1988; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Advisory Neighborhood Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - AFDC, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO, undated; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Aid to families with dependent children, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - AIDS, undated; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - AIDS data and report, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - AIDS funding, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - AIDS legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Airport Transfer Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Alamac/River Inn, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol Drug and Mental Illness Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Alcohol legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - All-Electric Rate - Pepco, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Alley Closing - Far East Trade Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Alley closing - Peter Kahn, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Alley closing - square 14, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Alley closing - square 15, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Alley closing - square 159, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Alley closing - square 166, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Alley closing - square 183 - 16th and L, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Alley closing - square 24, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Alley closing - square 29, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Alley closing - square 37, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Alley closing - square 74, undated; Series 3 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Alley closings - P and Q Streets NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Ambulance services, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - American Jewish Community, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - American Spotlight, Republic Properties Corporation, undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 16)
  - American University Campus Plan - zoning, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Amoco service stations, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Amoco stations - New Jersey Ave, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - ANC 2A minutes, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - ANC 2B Issues, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - ANC 2E, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - ANC Act, 1984; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - ANC Task Force final reports, 1983; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - ANCs, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Announcement speech, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Annual file, 1987; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Annual file, 1986; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report to the City Council, 1979; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Antioch general background, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Antioch Law School, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Antioch mark up, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Arch retrospective, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Area labor summary, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - ART Consignment legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Art galleries zoning case, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Art Shell reception, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Arthur Capper - 1011 7th Street SE, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Arthur Capper Sr - 6011 L Street SE, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Arthur Capper Family, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Arthur Capper Health Clinic, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Asbestos Licensing and Control Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Assignment to staff, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Audit of Public Housing, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Auditor, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Auto Repossession Law, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Automobile Consumer Protection, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Automotive Trade Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Award from the D.C. Commission on Baseball, Series 3 (Box 83, Item 8)
  - Badges (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Bail Amendment Act, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Bail bond reform, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Bail Reform Amendments, 1982; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Bank deposit records, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Bank records - Committee to Re-elect, 1982; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Bank statements, undated; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Bank statements, 1983; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Bank statements, undated; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 11)
  - Bank statements, undated; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 12)
  - Bank statements, undated; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 13)
  - Bank statements - Mayoral campaign, 1982; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Bank voucher forms, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Bankers, undated; Series 3 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Bankers association DC, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Banking, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Banking - Acquisition of American Security, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Banking - New DC banks, 1986; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Banking - New DC banks, 1986; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Banking - New DC banks, 1986; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Banking - News articles, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Banking legislation - acquisitions and mergers, 1986; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Banking regulations, undated; Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Banking regulations, undated; Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Barney Circle, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Beijing's Archway, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Benbow, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Best Friends of DC, undated; Series 3 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Beyond City Hall, Chairman Wilson, undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 24)
  - Beyond City Hall, Chairman Wilson [12 shows], undated; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 25)
  - Bias-Related Crime Act, 1989; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Bias-Related Crime Act - notes, 1989; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Bicentennial celebration plate, 1976; Series 3 (Box 83, Item 1)
  - Bill 7-28 - O.S.H.A, undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bill 7-81 "Look Alike Firearms", undated; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Black History, 1991; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 27)
  - Blackies zoning change, 1987; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Blagden Alley, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Blanche Auguer, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Blank volunteer sheets, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - BMHS Community, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Board of Election, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Board of Medicine, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Board of Zoning Adjustment, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Bobby McMahon, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - BOCA Laws, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Bonwit Plaza, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Boston House, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Boston Properties - alley closing, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Boston Properties - zoning case - 2301 N Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Boston Properties case, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Bottle bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Bowl from the Rotary Club of Washington, DC, undated; Series 3 (Box 86, Item 4)
  - Boxing commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Brass Rail - Franklin Square Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Bristol House - liquor license, undated; Series 3 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Brookings Institute, 1989; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Brookings Institute PUD, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Brunswick House, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Budget information, 1985; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Building restriction line, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Bulk rate mailing info, undated; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Bulk rate mailings, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Bulletproof vests, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Bundy School Playground, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Burglar alarm legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Bus ban - Foggy Bottom, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bus ban on G Street SW, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Bus routes, undated; Series 3 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bus shelters, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Buttons, Series 3 (Box 86, Item 2)
  - Buzzard Point Noise (PEPCO), undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - BZA Application 14001 Chandler - Judiciary Tower, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - BZA Case - Winthrop House, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - BZA Case 1136 6th Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - BZA Case 12013 Parking Lot, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - BZA Case 13658 1314 Mass Ave NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - BZA Case 13835 1727 21st St NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - BZA Case 14298 903 M Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - BZA Case 14413 924 N Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - BZA Case 14490 1523-1525 Sixteenth Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - BZA Case 14617 Doggett's Parking Lot, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - BZA Case 85-4 1329 L Street NW, undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Cable Franchise Act, 1981; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Cable TV Public Hearing, 1977 April 06; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Capital Children's Museum, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Capital Children's Museum, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Capital Children's Museum, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Capital Children's Museum Emergency, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Capital City Market - Artist Studio, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Capital Gateway, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Capital Gateway, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Capital Gateway, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Capital Gateway, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Capital Gateway, 1982-1983; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Capital Gateway, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Capital Hill Restoration Society Inc, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Capital Improvements, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Capitol Gateway Phase I Approval Res., undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Hospital, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Capitol Hill Police Sub-Station 1-D-1, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Capitol Park 800 4th Street SW, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Capitol Park Complex SW, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Capitol Park Towers - Twin Towers, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Carla Miller, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Carol Liege, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Carol Ridker's Party - CSF, 1984 January 27; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Carriage Horse letters, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Carriage Horses, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Carrollsburg Condo, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Carrollsburg sidewalk, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Carrollsburg Square, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Case Law/State statutes, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - CD One, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Census Data by ANC, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Census Tract Data, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Ceremonial Fund, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Ceremonial Resolutions, 1987; Series 3 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Certificates, 1980-1991; Series 3 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Certificates and programs, undated; Series 3 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Chairman's $25K Stipend, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Challenger Center - RLA Project, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Challenger Center - Southwest, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Chanceries, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Chancery expansion zoning case, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Ch. 9 John Wilson Park, 1993; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 1)
  - Channel 9, 1991 November 27; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 8)
  - Channel Inn, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Channel Inn, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Channell Square Apartments, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Chapter III Nighclub, undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Chartered Health Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Chastleton, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Check stubs, 1982; Series 3 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Checkbook, undated; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Checks - 1-12, undated; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Checks - 13-21, undated; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Checks - 22-35, undated; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Chevalier v. Wilson, 1992; Series 3 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Children's Museum - National Learning Center Financial Problems, 1987; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Children's Museum Emergency, undated; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Chinatown archway, undated; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Chinatown for Wilson, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Chinatown Housing Project, undated; Series 3 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Chinatown Recreation Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Community, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Choral Art Society of DC, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Christmas card, 1991; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Christmas Cards, 1989; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Christmas Cards, 1991; Series 3 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Christmas cards [blank, undated; Series 3 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Church pamphlets, undated; Series 3 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Churches in Ward 2, 1980; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Citizen Advisory Task Force on Neighborhood Municipal Off Street Parking, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - City Council press conference, 1992 October 29; Series 3 (Box 85, Videocassette 12)
  - City Council publications, undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - City Museum, undated; Series 3 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Claims, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Clarke bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Clinical Lab Act, 1988; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Clinical Lab Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Clinical Lab Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Clinical Lab Act, 1988; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Clinical Lab Act, 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Clinical Lab Act - Federal Legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Clinical Lab Act - Mass. Legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Clinical Lab Act - New York Legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Clinical Lab Act - Penn. Legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Clinical Lab Act - Work Papers, 1988; Series 3 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Clinical Lab Bill, 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Clinical Lab Bill - Testimony, 1988; Series 3 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1964-1991; Series 3 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1967-1992; Series 3 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Clippings about Wilson, 1992; Series 3 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Clock with inscription, Series 3 (Box 83, Item 9)
  - Closing of Public Alley Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - COG/RLA Project N. Capital Street, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Colonel Brooks Tavern rezoning, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Hospital, undated; Series 3 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Hospital Land Transfer, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Plaza, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Comments - Pay Equity, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Commission Appointments, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Committee filing records, undated; Series 3 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Government Operations, undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Committee organization reports, undated; Series 3 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Committee to Re-elect - bank statements, 1984; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 9)
  - Committee to Re-elect - copies of checks, 1983; Series 3 (Box 37B, Folder 8)
  - Committee to Re-elect John Wilson - Final Report, undated; Series 3 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Committee to Save Rental Housing, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Common Capital Fund, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Common Cause, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Community based residential facilities, undated; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Community Center - Northwest 1, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Community Development Block Grant - Tenth Year, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Community Development Block Grant - Thirteenth Year Program, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Community Development Block Grant #12, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Community Development Block Grant #15, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Community Development Block Grant #8, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Community Development Block Grant #9, undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Community Development Block Grant Program Resolution, 1983; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Community Health Care Inc., undated; Series 3 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Community Health Care Inc., undated; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Comprehensive Anti-Drunk Driving Legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Comprehensive Plan, undated; Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Comprehensive Plan Correspondence, undated; Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Comprehensive Plan legislation, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Comprehensive Plan Testimony, undated; Series 3 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Concerned Citizens Association, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Condo Clarification Amendment Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Condo Conversion Tenant Election Invalidation Case, 1987; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Condo Extension Bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Condo regulations, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Condominium back up, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Condominium Commission, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Condominium conversion, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Condominium conversion - JAW's amendments, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Condominium Conversion Act Foreclosures, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Condominium conversion issues, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Condominium Coop - Illegal Conversion Notices, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Condominium Coop Law Amdnements, undated; Series 3 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Condominium cooperative 180-day moratorium bill, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Condominium Moratorium Exemptions, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Condominiums in DC, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Congratulations, 1988; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Conominium New - Co-op Emergency, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Fundraiser, 1985 July 01; Series 3 (Box 37A, Folder 7)
  - Constituent response to council resolution on 2C proposal, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Constituents - Ward 2, undated; Series 3 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Constitutionality of Moratorium on Conversion of Rental Units to Condominium Cooperatives and Apartment Hotels, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Consumer and Regulatory Affairs Committee, 1986; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Consumer Protection - DC Office, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Consuming Alcohol During Pregnancy Act, 1985; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Contract Tax Enforcement Act, 1986; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Contract Tax Enforcement Act, 1987; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Contracting, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Control of Prostitution and Use of Dangerous Drugs, 1981; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Convention Center, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Convention Center - Recommendations, 1987; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Convention Center expansion, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Convention Center Food Contract, undated; Series 3 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Convention Center project, undated; Series 3 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Convention Center tax, undated; Series 3 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Conveyance of Jewish Community Center Act, 1989; Series 3 (Box 41, Folder 8)